<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-09-16T10:08:37+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Vivien Walter’s Website</title><subtitle>Website presenting all my research projects on the biophysics of lipid membranes.</subtitle><author><name>Vivien WALTER, PhD</name></author><entry><title type="html">New Website now online</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/general/website-online/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Website now online" /><published>2019-09-15T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-09-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/general/website-online</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/general/website-online/">&lt;p&gt;Welcome all to my &lt;strong&gt;brand new website&lt;/strong&gt;! I was a bit bored and tired of the previous version,
both because of the design but also because of the Django framework which is not fun at all
to edit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the transfer, I updated everything in the &lt;strong&gt;Research&lt;/strong&gt; section to make sure it really shows
what I am doing at the moment. I also replaced the Ressources section, which was showing too
many things and many useless ones to a simple &lt;strong&gt;Softwares&lt;/strong&gt; one. I also decided to put back
my &lt;strong&gt;Teaching&lt;/strong&gt; section, which I will fill over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are still things left to do, mostly adding content to the Teaching section, but it is going
to take so much time that I have decided to deploy the site now and fill the section later.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Vivien WALTER, PhD</name></author><category term="website" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Welcome all to my brand new website! I was a bit bored and tired of the previous version, both because of the design but also because of the Django framework which is not fun at all to edit. During the transfer, I updated everything in the Research section to make sure it really shows what I am doing at the moment. I also replaced the Ressources section, which was showing too many things and many useless ones to a simple Softwares one. I also decided to put back my Teaching section, which I will fill over time. There are still things left to do, mostly adding content to the Teaching section, but it is going to take so much time that I have decided to deploy the site now and fill the section later.</summary></entry></feed>